hovr.com 2010-11-22

# Hovr - Privacy Policy

## Hovr Privacy Policy

#### About Hovr Incorporated:

Hovr Incorporated ("Hovr") is an ad-supported mobile content and social network that allows our users to download quality, fun mobile games and other mobile applications and content for free, and ability to connect, compete and interact with other users in a compelling social environment. Hovr believes that similar to other forms of media and entertainment, mobile content should be available for free to the users, supported by the advertisements, without compromising on the user experience. Hovr’s aim is to deliver relevant advertisements that may be of interest to its users.

#### Hovr Privacy Notice:

Hovr greatly values the privacy of our users, customers, members and others who visit and use www.hovr.com, wap.hovr.com, and/or any of Hovr’s third party distribution and marketing partners (the "Hovr Site") (collectively or individually, "Users"). This Privacy Notice is incorporated into and is subject to the Hovr End User License Agreement ("EULA"). Your use of the Hovr Site and any personal information you provide on the Hovr Site remain subject to the terms of this Privacy Notice and our EULA.

Please contact Hovr with questions or comments about this Privacy Notice at privacy@hovr.com or by mail at 33 W 19th St, 3rd Fl, New York, NY 10011, USA. YOU SHOULD CAREFULLY READ THE FOLLOWING PRIVACY NOTICE BEFORE DOWNLOADING ANY HOVR MOBILE GAME APPLICATIONS. BY INSTALLING, COPYING OR OTHERWISE USING ANY HOVR MOBILE GAME APPLICATIONS AND/OR BY CLICKING THE "I ACCEPT" BUTTON (OR LINK) FROM YOUR MOBILE PHONE OR ON THE HOVR SITE, YOU ACKNOWLEDGE THAT YOU UNDERSTAND AND AGREE TO BE BOUND BY THE TERMS OF THIS PRIVACY NOTICE.

IMPORTANT NOTICE: By choosing to input your mobile phone number into any mobile game application Signup and/or download page and to download any mobile game, you expressly agree and consent to: (a) receive SMS communications from Hovr and (b) automatically receive advertisements from Hovr on your mobile device within the games you download.

#### The Information Hovr Collects:

  * User-provided Information: To download a mobile game application from Hovr, you must sign in to Hovr service by choosing a valid username and password, and providing some basic information such as your email address, country, postal code, gender, date of birth, carrier, handset manufacturer, handset model and your wireless cell phone number.
  * "Cookies" Information: When you visit the Hovr Site, we may send one or more cookies - small text files containing a string of alphanumeric characters - to your computer. Hovr uses both session cookies and persistent cookies. A session cookie disappears after you close your browser. A persistent cookie remains after you close your browser and may be used by your browser on subsequent visits to the Hovr Site. Persistent cookies can be removed. Please review your web browser "Help" file to learn the proper way to modify your cookie settings.
  * "Automatically Collected" Information: When you visit the Hovr Site or open an HTML email from Hovr, we may automatically record certain information from your web browser by using different types of technology, including "clear gifs" or "web beacons." This "automatically collected" information may include unique "device IDs" (similar to IP addresses), Internet Protocol address ("IP Address"), web browser type, the web pages or sites that you visit just before or just after the Hovr Site, the pages you view on our site, and the dates and times that you visit the Hovr Site.
  * Personal Sensitive Information: Hovr will NEVER ask you for certain types of personal sensitive information such as your social security number, passport number, credit card number or any other such sensitive personal or financial information.

#### The Way Hovr Uses Information:

  * Hovr uses the mobile phone number that you provide to send to you a text message via short message service ("SMS"), at your request, which includes a download link to the mobile game application of your choice. Hovr does not send more than the requested SMS text messages and retains phone number for sending additional games you may request in the future .
  * Hovr uses "user-provided," "automatically collected," and "cookies" information to deliver to your mobile device customized third-party advertisements and content. We will use best effort to deliver you the most relevant and targeted advertisements and content, which may be of interest to you.
  * Hovr may use your email address or send a text message via SMS to your mobile phone number, without further consent, for administrative purposes such as notifying you of major Hovr Site updates, for customer service purposes, or to contact you regarding any game application that you have downloaded.
  * Hovr may use any of the information that we collect to operate, maintain, enhance, and provide to Users all of the features found on the Hovr Site.
  * Hovr may use any of the information that we collect to understand the usage trends and preferences of our Users, to improve the way the Hovr Site works and looks, and to create new features and functionality.
  * Hovr may use "automatically collected" and "cookies" information to: (a) remember your information so that you will not have to re-enter it during your visit or the next time you visit the Hovr Site; (b) monitor the effectiveness of third-party marketing campaigns; (c) monitor aggregate site usage metrics such as total number of visitors and pages viewed; and (d) track your entries, submissions, and status in any promotions, sweepstakes, and contests.
  * Hovr will not use your email address, phone number or other personally identifiable information to send promotional or marketing messages without your consent or except as part of a specific program or feature for which you will have the ability to opt-in.

#### When Hovr Discloses Information:

  * Hovr does not share your personally identifiable information with other organizations for their marketing or promotional uses without your express consent. 
  * Hovr discloses usage information, automatically collected and other aggregate non-personally-identifiable information (such as advertisement viewership data and advertisement viewership demographic data) with interested third parties to assist them in understanding the usage, viewing, and demographic patterns for certain advertisements, content, programs, services, promotions, and/or functionality within Hovr mobile game applications and the Hovr Site.
  * To provide web site hosting, maintenance and security, fulfill orders, offer certain functionality, improve our site, and create new site features, we may disclose User information to affiliated companies or other businesses or persons. We require that these parties process such information in compliance with this Privacy Notice, we authorize only a limited use of such information, and we require these parties to use appropriate confidentiality measures.
  * Hovr may disclose User information if required to do so by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with state and federal laws or respond to a court order, judicial or other government subpoena, or warrant. We may make such disclosures without providing Users notice, in some cases.
  * Hovr also reserves the right to disclose User information that we believe, in good faith, is appropriate or necessary to take precautions against liability; protect Hovr from fraudulent, abusive, or unlawful uses; to investigate and defend ourselves against any third-party claims or allegations; to assist government enforcement agencies; to protect the security or integrity of the Hovr Site; and to protect the rights, property, or personal safety of Hovr, our Users, or others.

#### Your Choices:

  * You may, decline to share your phone number or other personally-identifiable information with Hovr, in which case Hovr will not be able to provide to you the mobile game applications on the Hovr Site. You may update, correct, or delete your member information and email subscription preferences at any time by going to the account section of the Hovr Site.
  * To protect your privacy and security, we take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting you account access or making corrections. YOU ARE RESPONSIBLE FOR MAINTAINING THE SECRECY OF YOUR UNIQUE PASSWORD, SECRET QUESTION AND ACCOUNT INFORMATION AT ALL TIMES.

#### Third-party Advertisers, Links to Other Sites:

  * Hovr may allow other companies, called third-party ad servers or ad networks, to serve advertisements within the Hovr Services or Hovr mobile game applications. These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to send, directly to your browser and/or mobile device, the advertisements and links that appear on the Hovr Services or within Hovr mobile game applications. They may automatically receive your IP address when this happens. They may also use other technologies (such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons) to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and to personalize the advertising content in effort to make it more relevant.
  * You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers or ad networks. Hovr's privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.
  * Hovr will not share your personal information with third party ad servers and ad networks, unless you opt-in and provide such information yourself to receive materials from them. Hovr does not provide any personally identifiable information to these third-party ad servers or ad networks without your consent or except as part of a specific program or feature for which you will have the ability to opt-in.

#### Our Commitment to Data Security:

  * Hovr uses commercially reasonable physical, managerial, and technical safeguards to preserve the integrity and security of your personal information. We do our best to keep all your personal information and data secure. We cannot, however, ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit, and you do so at your own risk. Once we receive your transmission of information, Hovr makes commercially reasonable best efforts to ensure the security of our systems. However, please note that this is not a guarantee that such information may not be accessed, disclosed, altered, or destroyed by breach of any of our physical, technical, or managerial safeguards.
  * If Hovr learns of a security systems breach, then we may attempt to notify you electronically so that you can take appropriate protective steps. Hovr may also post a notice on the Hovr Site if a security breach occurs. Depending on where you live, you may have a legal right to receive notice of a security breach in writing. To receive a free written notice of a security breach you should notify us at privacy@hovr.com.

#### Our Commitment to Children's Privacy:

  * Protecting the privacy of young children is especially important. For that reason, Hovr does not knowingly collect or maintain personally identifiable information on the Hovr Site from persons under 13 years of age, and no part of the Hovr site is directed to persons under 13. IF YOU ARE UNDER 13 YEARS OF AGE, THEN PLEASE DO NOT USE OR ACCESS THE HOVR SITE AT ANY TIME OR IN ANY MANNER. If Hovr learns that personally-identifiable information of persons less than 13-years-of-age has been collected on Hovr without verifiable parental consent, then Hovr will take the appropriate steps to delete this information.

#### International Visitors:

  * The Hovr Site is hosted in the United States and is intended for United States visitors. If you are using the Hovr Site or any Hovr mobile game applications from the European Union, Asia, South America, Africa or other regions with laws governing data collection and use that may differ from U.S. law, please note that you are transferring your personal data to the United States and by providing your personal data you consent to that transfer.

#### In the Event of Merger, Sale, or Bankruptcy:

  * In the event that Hovr is acquired by or merged with a third-party entity, we reserve the right, in any of these circumstances, to transfer or assign the information we have collected from Users as part of such merger, acquisition, sale, or other change of control. In the unlikely event of our bankruptcy, insolvency, reorganization, receivership, or assignment for the benefit of creditors, or the application of laws or equitable principles affecting creditors' rights generally, we may not be able to control how your personal information is treated, transferred, or used.

#### Changes and Updates to this Privacy Notice:

  * This Privacy Notice may be revised periodically without further notice to you and this will be reflected by the "last modified" notice below. Please revisit this page to stay aware of any changes. In general, we only use your personal information in the manner described in the Privacy Notice in effect when we received that personal information. Your continued use of the Hovr Site constitutes your agreement to this Privacy Notice and any future revisions.
  * For revisions to this Privacy Notice that may be materially less restrictive on our use or disclosure of personal information you have provided to us, we will make reasonable efforts to notify you and obtain your consent before implementing such revisions with respect to such information.

Effective Date, Date Last Modified: This Privacy Notice is effective as of November 15th, 2006. Hovr Contact Information: Please contact Hovr with any questions or comments about this Privacy Notice, your personal information, our third-party disclosure practices, or your consent choices at privacy@hovr.com or by postal mail at 33 W 19th St, 3rd Fl, New York, NY 10011. We will respond to your inquiry as soon as possible, and within 30 days of its receipt.
